{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "The moon is believed to be ___ the sun.",
      "a": "less brighter than",
      "b": "very smaller than",
      "c": "much less bright than",
      "d": "much smaller than",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": ".\n- Much / More + Adj\n+Use much (adv.) to emphasize  a comparative adjective, -er. \t",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Watson knows little of Chinese, _________ of Italian.",
      "a": "and still less",
      "b": "as well as",
      "c": "and still more",
      "d": "no less than",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Comparison of Inferiority: Less + adj \n+ Little- less- least",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Francis's composition proved ___ than that of others.",
      "a": "not much better",
      "b": "no more better",
      "c": "no more as good",
      "d": "not much as good",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": ".\n-Much / More + Adj\n+Use much (adv.) to emphasize  a comparative adjective, -er. \t",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "I was very busy. \"Did you really work hard ___ ?\"",
      "a": "all the day long",
      "b": "all day",
      "c": "all of day long",
      "d": "the all day",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": ". \n- All day (long): during the whole time you are awake",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "What about our son's math examination? \"Excellent! He made ___ no mistake this time.\"",
      "a": "nearly",
      "b": "almost",
      "c": "mostly",
      "d": "hardly",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Mostly = of all the options, this is the majority. \n- Almost = good enough but not perfect. \n- Nearly = very close to the optimal position but not quite there. \n- Hardly= seldom",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The manager is busy all the time; he is not ___ at home on the weekends.",
      "a": "mostly",
      "b": "hardly",
      "c": "always",
      "d": "nearly",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": ".\n- Always: all the time, at all times, or every time\n-Mostly = of all the options, this is the majority. \n-Almost = good enough but not perfect.\n-Nearly = very close to the optimal position but not quite there.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which skirt do you think looks ___, the long one or the short one?",
      "a": "good",
      "b": "well",
      "c": "best",
      "d": "better",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Comparative: used when comparing two things \n+ Good/well-&gt; better",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Amy sings _________ out of all the singers in the country.",
      "a": "most beautiful",
      "b": "the most beautiful",
      "c": "much more beautiful",
      "d": "the most beautifully",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Superlative you talk about one thing only and how it is the best, worst, etc. You do not compare two things \n+ The most+ adj/ adj+est",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who writes ___ of the four girls?",
      "a": "well",
      "b": "the best",
      "c": "good",
      "d": "better",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- Superlative you talk about one thing only and how it is the best, worst, etc. You do not compare two things \n+ The most+ adj/ adj+est \n+ Best (irregular adj): good/well-better- best ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Nile is _________ river in the world.",
      "a": "the second long",
      "b": "second longest",
      "c": "the second longer",
      "d": "the second longest",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": ".",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "7",
      "subcategorylv2": "8",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}